over25tips.com 2019-02-20

# Privacy policy at Over25Tips.com

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Over25Tips.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from visitors.

 **Personal identification information**   
We may collect personal identification information from visitors in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on Over25Tips.com. We will collect personal identification information from visitors only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. visitors can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

 **Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about visitors whenever they interact with Over25Tips.com. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about visitors means of connection to Over25Tips.com, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**   
Over25Tips.com may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **How we use collected information**   
Over25Tips.com may collect and use visitors personal information for the following purposes:

1\. To run and operate Over25Tips.com - we may need your information display content on the site correctly.  
2\. To personalize user experience - we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our visitors as a group use the services and resources provided on Over25Tips.com.

 **Our cookies**   
We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services.

 **How we protect your information**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on Over25Tips.com.

 **Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent visitors personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

 **Third party websites**  
Visitors may find advertising or other content on Over25Tips.com that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from Over25Tips.com. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to Over25Tips.com, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

 **Advertising**  
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to visitors by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using Over25Tips.com, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use Over25Tips.com. Your continued use of Over25Tips.com following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
